Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
[airplane engine roaring]
[هدير محرك الطائرة]
[tires screeching]
[صراخ الإطارات]
[upbeat music]
[موسيقى مبهجة]
* Yeah! I don't know if I ever seen this before *
*أجل! لا أعرف إن كنت قد رأيت هذا من قبل*
* Better hold tight Better know the score *
* من الأفضل أن تتمسك بقوة، ومن الأفضل أن تعرف النتيجة *
* How do you like me *
*كيف يعجبك*
* I'm lookin' so freshin' good *
*أنا أبدو منتعشًا جدًا*
* Now keep your eyes open *
*الآن أبقي عينيك مفتوحتين*
* [indistinct *
* [غير واضح *
* 'Cause you gotta watch *
*لأنك يجب أن تشاهد*
* 'Cause you gotta watch this *
* لأنك يجب أن تشاهد هذا *
* 'Cause you gotta watch it *
*لأنك يجب أن تشاهده*
[bell ringing]
[رنين الجرس]
- Good morning. I'm Tracy Savage with Wake Up, LA.
صباح الخير. معكم تريسي سافاج من برنامج "استيقظ يا لوس أنجلوس".
This morning, Vice President Davis is back
هذا الصباح، نائب الرئيس ديفيس عاد
in Southern California.
في جنوب كاليفورنيا
What's on the VP's agenda today, Marty?
ما هو جدول أعمال نائب الرئيس اليوم يا مارتي؟
- The vice president has a packed schedule
- نائب الرئيس لديه جدول أعمال مزدحم
while he's here.
بينما هو هنا
The first event is a rally inside City Hall.
الحدث الأول هو تجمع جماهيري داخل مبنى البلدية.
The second is this Hollywood fundraiser gala
والثاني هو حفل جمع التبرعات في هوليوود
where some of the biggest celebrities in town
حيث يوجد بعض من أكبر المشاهير في المدينة
will be there supporting him
سوف أكون هناك لدعمه
and the president in their push for a cleaner, greener economy.
والرئيس في سعيهما إلى اقتصاد أنظف وأكثر خضرة.
- I don't remember the homeless problem being this bad.
- لا أتذكر أن مشكلة المشردين كانت بهذا السوء.
- Yeah. Pretty tough situation on everybody.
- نعم. وضع صعب جدًا على الجميع.
City's doing best they can.
المدينة تبذل قصارى جهدها.
- They've spent like 22 million so far
- لقد أنفقوا حوالي 22 مليونًا حتى الآن
and only moved like 18 people.
وانتقل حوالي 18 شخصًا فقط.
I heard DC is pretty bad, too.
سمعت أن DC سيئة جدًا أيضًا.
That's where you're based now, right?
هذا هو المكان الذي تتواجد فيه الآن، أليس كذلك؟
Going on two weeks.
مضى اسبوعين.
They yanked me out of London,
لقد انتزعوني من لندن،
and I was just starting to like it too.
وبدأت أحبه أيضًا.
Had my bike. You know, loop around the canal.
كانت معي دراجتي. تعرف، أدور حول القناة.
What can you do when Mercury 2 asks for you personally?
ماذا يمكنك أن تفعل عندما يطلب منك عطارد 2 شخصيًا؟
Oh, you were invited personally?
أوه، لقد تم دعوتك شخصيا؟
Look at you, Mr. Favorite One.
أنظر إليك يا سيد المفضل.
Definitely not the favorite.
بالتأكيد ليس المفضل.
Just... right place, right time, I guess.
فقط... المكان المناسب، والوقت المناسب، على ما أعتقد.
[dreary music]
[موسيقى كئيبة]
[security scanning]
[الفحص الأمني]
[door unlocks]
[يُفتح الباب]
[sirens wailing]
[صفارات الإنذار تصرخ]
Is that what I think it is?
هل هذا ما أعتقد أنه كذلك؟
- Damn, this could be more stressful
- اللعنة، هذا قد يكون أكثر إرهاقًا
than the POTUS detail, huh?
من تفاصيل رئيس الولايات المتحدة، أليس كذلك؟
Why is that?
لماذا هذا؟
Shit, think about it.
يا إلهي، فكر في الأمر.
I mean, we do the same job,
أعني أننا نقوم بنفس العمل،
way more engagements, with half the staff,
المزيد من المشاركات مع نصف الموظفين،
half the support, and--
نصف الدعم، و--
(in unison) Half the pay.
(بالانسجام) نصف الأجر.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
[tense music]
[موسيقى متوترة]
[buttons beeping]
[أزرار تصدر صوت تنبيه]
[security device pings]
[إشارات جهاز الأمان]
[lock beeps]
[صوت صفير القفل]
[sirens wailing]
[صفارات الإنذار تصرخ]
[phone beeps, ringing on the other side]
[صوت صفير الهاتف، رنين على الجانب الآخر]
Hold it.
إمسكها.
[Owens] Go.
[أوينز] اذهب.
- [Pearson] Special Agent Owens. ETA, three minutes.
- [بيرسون] العميل الخاص أوينز الوقت المتوقع للوصول هو ثلاث دقائق.
Prepare for the exchange.
الاستعداد للتبادل
We'll have 30 seconds.
سيكون لدينا 30 ثانية.
[sirens wailing, intense music]
[عويل صفارات الإنذار، موسيقى مكثفة]
Hey! Go back! Get back!
هيا! ارجع! ارجع!
You can't be here.
لا يمكنك أن تكون هنا.
[sirens wailing]
[صفارات الإنذار تصرخ]
Turn around!
استدر!
Turn--! [gun shots]
انعطف--! [طلقات نارية]
[intense music] [screams]
[موسيقى مكثفة] [صراخ]
- [Jackson] What the hell is that?
- [جاكسون] ما هذا بحق الجحيم؟
[Pearson] Suspect, left side.
[بيرسون] المشتبه به، الجانب الأيسر.
[Jackson] It's an attack. [Choi] Move it!
[جاكسون] إنه هجوم. [تشوي] تحرك!
-  [Jackson] Go, go, go. -  [Pearson] Watch out!
-  [جاكسون] اذهب، اذهب، اذهب. -  [بيرسون] احترس!
[explosion]
[انفجار]
[crowd screams]
[صراخ الحشد]
- [Agent] What was that? -  [Agent Two] Call it in.
- [العميل] ما هذا؟ -  [العميل الثاني] أبلغ عنه.
[Agent Three] ...all stations.
[العميل الثالث] ...جميع المحطات.
[siren wailing]
[عويل صفارات الإنذار]
- [Female Agent] Officer down.
- [العميلة] ضابط سقط.
- [Choi] Mercury 2 under attack. Relocation.
- [تشوي] ميركوري 2 تحت الهجوم. الانتقال.
Need air support.
بحاجة إلى دعم جوي.
[loud explosion]
[انفجار قوي]
It's a professional hit.
إنها ضربة احترافية.
- We gotta get off the [indistinct]!
- علينا أن نخرج من [غير واضح]!
- What are you doing? Drive!
- ماذا تفعل؟ قيادة!
[gun shots]
[طلقات نارية]
Jackson! Jackson!
جاكسون! جاكسون!
[automatic gunfire]
[إطلاق نار أوتوماتيكي]
[Owens] Reeves!
[أوينز] ريفز
[gun fire]
[إطلاق نار]
- Stay with me. Hold on.
- ابق معي. انتظر.
[hoarsely] Take it. Take it.
[بصوت أجش] خذها. خذها.
You have to take it.
يجب عليك أن تأخذها.
Huh?
هاه؟
[gunfire, bullets ricocheting]
[إطلاق نار، رصاصات مرتدة]
[Reeves groans]
[ريفز يتأوه]
[Owens] Get up. Come on.
[أوينز] انهض. هيا.
Come on, let's go.
هيا بنا نذهب
I know it hurts.
أعلم أن الأمر مؤلم.
Come on.
تعال
[smoke hissing]
[هسهسة الدخان]
[bullets ricocheting]
[ارتداد الرصاص]
[Jackson groaning]
[جاكسون يتأوه]
[explosion]
[انفجار]
[gunfire]
[إطلاق نار]
[Gunman One] Ugh! Fuck!
[المسلح الأول] آه! اللعنة!
[Gunman Two] Engage!.
[المسلح الثاني] انخرط!
[suspenseful music]
[موسيقى مشوقة]
- [Gunman Two] Where is he, God damn it?
- [المسلح الثاني] أين هو يا إلهي؟
- [Gunman Three] Get out of here. - [Gunman Two] He's not here.
- [المسلح الثالث] اخرج من هنا - [المسلح الثاني] إنه ليس هنا
- [Gunman Four] She doesn't have it. Check him.
- [المسلح الرابع] ليس لديها. تحقق منه.
- [Gunman Five] Cops are 30 seconds out.
- [الرجل المسلح رقم خمسة] الشرطة على بعد 30 ثانية.
Fuck!
اللعنة!
[sirens wailing]
[صفارات الإنذار تصرخ]
- We have breaking news to report.
- لدينا أخبار عاجلة لنبلغكم بها.
Multiple explosions have rocked the downtown Los Angeles area.
هزت انفجارات متعددة منطقة وسط مدينة لوس أنجلوس.
Unconfirmed reports say that the vice president's motorcade
تشير تقارير غير مؤكدة إلى أن موكب نائب الرئيس
was at the center of these attacks,
كان في مركز هذه الهجمات،
with a secondary explosion right near LA City Hall.
مع انفجار ثانوي بالقرب من مبنى بلدية لوس أنجلوس.
A chemical substance may have been deployed
ربما تم نشر مادة كيميائية
at this City Hall attack.
في هذا الهجوم على مبنى البلدية
[sirens wailing]
[صفارات الإنذار تصرخ]
- Hey, hey, hey. - [Jogger] Whoa.
- هي، هي، هي. - [عدّاء] واو.
I need your phone.
أحتاج هاتفك.
[Jogger] What?
[العداء] ماذا؟
- [Choi] Please. -  [Jogger] Hey.
- [تشوي] من فضلك.< /i> -  [العداء] مرحبًا.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث؟
- Thank you. - [Jogger] Hey.
- شكرا لك. - [العداء] مرحبا.
[siren wailing]
[عويل صفارات الإنذار]
- [Pilot] RNGR1, heading downtown,
- [الطيار] RNGR1، متجهًا إلى وسط المدينة
approaching Concert Hall. Wilson and Grant.
يقترب من قاعة الحفلات الموسيقية. ويلسون وجرانت.
ETA, one minute out. Multiple explosions.
ETA، دقيقة واحدة متبقية. انفجارات متعددة.
Vice president's motorcade. En route to 110 freeway.
موكب نائب الرئيس. في طريقه إلى الطريق السريع ١١٠.
[phone ringing]
[رنين الهاتف]
- [female voice on phone] Identification.
- [صوت أنثوي على الهاتف] التعريف
45759 Charlie.
45759 تشارلي.
Connecting.
جاري الاتصال
- Choi, it's General Marshall. What's going on?
- تشوي، أنا الجنرال مارشال. ماذا يحدث؟
We've got reports.
لقد حصلنا على تقارير.
Our motorcade was ambushed.
لقد تعرض موكبنا لكمين.
High-grade explosives,
متفجرات عالية الجودة،
high-grade ops.
عمليات عالية الجودة.
Well thought out, well executed.
مدروسة جيدًا، منفذة جيدًا.
Cadillac One is intact, but we've been split.
كاديلاك ون سليمة، لكننا انقسمنا.
- Where? Jackson with you?
- أين؟ جاكسون معك؟
We are down one
نحن أسفل واحد
permanently.
دائمًا.
Our driver was involved. They shot him.
سائقنا كان متورطًا. أطلقوا عليه النار.
They killed Pearson, and they nearly got me too.
لقد قتلوا بيرسون، وكادوا أن يقتلوني أيضًا.
Jesus.
عيسى.
Jackson was carrying the football.
جاكسون كان يحمل كرة القدم.
I got it.
حصلت عليه.
But I'm all alone out here.
ولكنني وحدي هنا.
We're initializing protocol.
نحن نقوم بتهيئة البروتوكول.
Whiskey Mike Delta.
ويسكي مايك دلتا.
It's on.
إنه على.
What the fuck?
ماذا بحق الجحيم؟
Where do I go? What do I do?
أين أذهب؟ ماذا أفعل؟
- All agents downtown are ordered to the nearest safe house.
- تم إصدار أوامر لجميع العملاء في وسط المدينة بالتوجه إلى أقرب منزل آمن.
- Jesus. I need an extraction, not a safe house.
- يسوع. أحتاج إلى عملية استئصال، وليس إلى منزل آمن.
Go to 22404 Wilshire Boulevard.
اذهب إلى 22404 Wilshire Boulevard.
Shelter until further notice.
مأوى حتى إشعار آخر.
and keep it safe.
والحفاظ عليه آمنًا.
Call me from a secure line once you get there.
اتصل بي من خط آمن بمجرد وصولك إلى هناك.
And Choi... don't trust anyone.
وتشوي... لا تثق بأحد.
Roger.
روجر.
[pensive music]
[موسيقى تأملية]
[phone alarm blaring]
[صوت إنذار الهاتف يرن]
[intense music]
[موسيقى مكثفة]
[rapid beeping]
[صوت صفير سريع]
Housekeeping.
التدبير المنزلي.
[Marshall] This is control.
[مارشال] هذا هو السيطرة.
What's the authorization for Safe House 5102?
ما هو الترخيص لـ Safe House 5102؟
This is Anderson.
هذا هو أندرسون.
Today's code is... Shit.
كود اليوم هو... شيت.
Ho--hold on.
هو--انتظر.
- [Marshall] Authorization for Safe House 5102?
- [مارشال] التفويض للبيت الآمن 5102؟
Yes, I hear you.
نعم أسمعك.
Today's code is Tango Charlie Romeo Romeo Five.
كود اليوم هو تانجو تشارلي روميو روميو فايف.
- Authorization accepted for safe house 5102.
- تم قبول الترخيص للبيت الآمن 5102.
[Anderson sighs]
[تنهد أندرسون]
-  [Marshall] We have initiated a shelter in place order.
-  [مارشال] لقد بدأنا أمر البقاء في المنزل.
It's a Whiskey Mike Delta situation.
إنه موقف دلتا ويسكي مايك
WMD.
أسلحة الدمار الشامل.
That's weapon of mass destruction.
هذا سلاح الدمار الشامل.
- Please prepare for three walk-ins.
- يرجى الاستعداد لثلاثة زيارات.
Proceed as planned.
إستمر ​​كما هو مخطط له.
[Anderson] Key code.
[أندرسون] رمز المفتاح
Washington.
واشنطن.
Understood.
مفهومة.
[rapid beeping]
[صوت صفير سريع]
Housekeeping.
التدبير المنزلي.
- Tango Charlie Romeo Romeo Five.
- تانجو تشارلي روميو روميو فايف.
- A--a--again.
- أ-أ-مرة أخرى.
- Tango Charlie Romeo Romeo Five.
- تانجو تشارلي روميو روميو فايف.
- Key code. I--I need the key code.
- رمز المفتاح. أحتاج إلى رمز المفتاح.
What?
ماذا؟
It's Washington.
إنها واشنطن.
Hurry, we've got an injury here.
اسرعوا، لدينا إصابة هنا.
- [Choi] Wa--Washington.
- [تشوي] وا--واشنطن.
Copy.
ينسخ.
[door buzzes]
[طنين الباب]
Okay.
تمام.
You got this.
لقد حصلت على هذا.
[rhythmic, tense music]
[موسيقى إيقاعية متوترة]
- [female voice on TV] Things are moving very quickly
- [صوت أنثوي على شاشة التلفزيون] الأمور تتحرك بسرعة كبيرة
in Washington, DC.
في واشنطن العاصمة
The White House is reporting that the president
البيت الأبيض يقول إن الرئيس
has been moved to a secure location.
تم نقله إلى مكان آمن.
Back here on the West Coast,
هنا على الساحل الغربي
the LAPD has already evacuated most of the residents
لقد قامت شرطة لوس أنجلوس بالفعل بإجلاء معظم السكان
and the workers from the downtown LA area.
والعمال من منطقة وسط مدينة لوس أنجلوس.
We're going to go live now to Skye Matthews,
سنبدأ البث المباشر الآن مع سكاي ماثيوز،
who is reporting from the perimeter--
من الذي يقوم بالإبلاغ من المحيط--
[door opens]
[يفتح الباب]
He's hurt.
لقد أصيب.
Hey, hey, hey.
مهلا، مهلا، مهلا.
Hey. Easy.
مهلا. سهل.
The bedroom's upstairs.
غرفة النوم في الطابق العلوي.
You all right?
هل انت بخير؟
I need a secured phone line.
أحتاج إلى خط هاتف آمن.
Jesus. Careful.
يسوع. كن حذرا.
- [Anderson] What happened?
- [أندرسون] ماذا حدث؟
- Waiting outside City Hall for the Mercury 2.
- الانتظار خارج مبنى البلدية لعطارد 2.
There was an explosion, some type of chemical.
كان هناك انفجار، نوع من المواد الكيميائية.
[Anderson] Chemical?
[أندرسون] كيميائي؟
Do you have a sniffer?
هل لديك جهاز شم؟
Yeah.
نعم.
[sniffer beeps]
[صوت صفير الشم]
CS gas.
غاز CS.
- Non-lethal.
- غير قاتلة.
I've seen it in action before.
لقد رأيته في العمل من قبل.
I know the signs.
أنا أعرف العلامات.
I was upwind, but he got the brunt of it.
لقد كنت في اتجاه الريح، لكنه تحمل العبء الأكبر.
The more time I spend here explaining this,
كلما قضيت وقتًا أطول هنا في شرح هذا الأمر،
the worse he gets.
كلما ازداد الأمر سوءا.
I need a med kit.
أحتاج إلى مجموعة أدوات طبية.
Um...um...
اممممم...اممم...
[Owens] Where?
[أوينز] أين؟
The fridge.
الثلاجة.
[distant siren wailing]
[صوت صفارة الإنذار البعيدة]
- Come on, keep pounding it.
- هيا، استمر في الضرب.
That's it, flush it out.
هذا هو الأمر، قم بإخراجه.
[rapid beeping]
[صوت صفير سريع]
We're fine here. Go answer it.
نحن بخير هنا. اذهب وأجب.
- [Reeves inhales sharply] - It's okay.
- [ريفز يستنشق بقوة] - لا بأس.
What are you waiting for?
ماذا تنتظر؟
- [Anderson] I was only told three guests.
- [أندرسون] لقد قيل لي أن هناك ثلاثة ضيوف فقط.
[footsteps receding]
[خطوات تتراجع]
[Anderson] Authorization.
[أندرسون] التفويض.
- [Sorello] Tango Charlie Romeo Romeo Five!
- [سوريلو] تانجو تشارلي روميو روميو فايف!
Key code?
رمز المفتاح؟
[Sorello] Washington.
[سوريلو] واشنطن
Come on.
تعال.
- [security buzzes] - [door unlocks]
- [أصوات تنبيه أمنية] - [فتح الباب]
Come on.
تعال.
[eerie music]
[موسيقى غريبة]
[Reeves exhales]
[ريفز يزفر]
- There's a new walk-in coming.
- هناك مشيًا جديدًا قادمًا.
You were at City Hall?
هل كنت في مبنى البلدية؟
- Wait, where were you? Were you at the motorcade?
- لحظة، أين كنت؟ هل كنت في الموكب؟
Yeah.
نعم.
I'm okay. Go.
انا بخير. اذهب.
Hands in the air.
الأيدي في الهواء.
Whoa, whoa. Nope, nope,
واو، واو. لا، لا،
Don't move. Don't move.
لا تتحرك. لا تتحرك.
I'm Anderson.
انا اندرسون.
I'm the housekeeper here.
أنا مدبرة المنزل هنا.
- I just almost got my ass blown apart.
- لقد كاد مؤخرتي أن تنفجر.
Lower your gun.
اخفض بندقيتك.
[tense music]
[موسيقى متوترة]
I went through hell out there.
لقد مررت بالجحيم هناك.
We all did.
لقد فعلنا ذلك جميعا.
Listen, I know we're all as scared as you are.
اسمع، أنا أعلم أننا جميعا خائفون مثلك.
I am not scared.
أنا لست خائفة.
I'm dialed in.
لقد تم الاتصال بي.
Anyone should be scared, it's whoever just attacked us,
يجب على أي شخص أن يخاف، فمن هاجمنا للتو،
and until I know exactly who they are...
وحتى أعرف بالضبط من هم...
and who you are...
ومن أنت...
I'm keeping my gun up.
أنا أبقي سلاحي في الأعلى.
Put the gun down.
ضع البندقية جانبا.
Put the gun down!
ضع البندقية إلى الأسفل!
How did you get in here?
كيف وصلت إلى هنا؟
[Halton] Used my own clearance.
[هالتون] استخدمت تصريحي الخاص.
[Sorello] Who the hell are you?
[سوريلو] من أنت بحق الجحيم؟
Halton Langley.
هالتون لانجلي.
- Sorello, Homeland Security. Show me your credentials.
- سوريلو، الأمن الداخلي. أرني أوراق اعتمادك.
Lower your gun and I will.
اخفض مسدسك وسوف أفعل ذلك.
And since when is a revolver standard at Homeland Security?
ومنذ متى كان المسدس هو المعيار في وزارة الأمن الداخلي؟
- Nothing about today has been standard.
- لم يكن هناك شيء قياسي اليوم .
- Well, I'd like to finish the day without getting shot.
- حسنًا، أود أن أنهي اليوم دون أن أُصاب برصاصة.
You?
أنت؟
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[تزداد الموسيقى المشوقة]
[music fades]
[تتلاشى الموسيقى]
See how easy things are when you just talk to people?
هل ترى مدى سهولة الأمور عندما تتحدث فقط مع الناس؟
[door locks]
[أقفال الأبواب]
Anderson. Housekeeping.
أندرسون. التدبير المنزلي.
Who are our guests?
من هم ضيوفنا؟
Mia Owens, DoD.
ميا أوينز، وزارة الدفاع.
My partner, Reeves, is injured.
شريكي ريفز مصاب.
He's upstairs.
إنه في الطابق العلوي.
Choi.
تشوي.
I heard you were part of the Mercury 2 detail.
سمعت أنك كنت جزءًا من تفاصيل ميركوري 2.
What is that?
ما هذا؟
Vice president.
نائب الرئيس.
- Just you running this house, Anderson?
- هل أنت فقط من يدير هذا المنزل، أندرسون؟
- [Anderson] Yes, sir. - Tough job by yourself.
- [أندرسون] نعم سيدي - مهمة صعبة بمفردك.
I spent time in this space back in the day.
لقد قضيت وقتا في هذه المساحة في الماضي.
Do we have comms?
هل لدينا اتصالات؟
[Anderson] Secured.
[أندرسون] مؤمن
- Yeah. What about those windows?
- نعم. ماذا عن تلك النوافذ؟
- They're one-way glass.
-إنهم زجاج ذو اتجاه واحد.
- Like the kid said, one-way glass.
- كما قال الطفل، زجاج ذو اتجاه واحد.
Bulletproof.
مضاد للرصاص.
What are you looking at? Huh?
ماذا تنظر إليه؟ هاه؟
Hey. He's not our problem.
مهلا، إنه ليس مشكلتنا.
[Sorello] You running point.
[سوريلو] نقطة تشغيلك
I'm not even here, man.
أنا لست هنا حتى، يا رجل.
- All right. I'm calling rank.
- حسنًا، سأتصل بالرتبة.
- I need to get to a secured phone line. Now.
أحتاج للاتصال بخط هاتف آمن الآن.
Follow me.
اتبعني.
- Halton. I need to go check on Reeves.
- هالتون، أريد أن أطمئن على ريفز.
Let me look at him.
دعني أنظر إليه.
[beep]
[زمارة]
Alone.
وحيد.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Close the door.
أغلق الباب.
[door closes]
[يُغلق الباب]
[Woman] Identification?
[امرأة] التعريف؟
- Choi. Pass code 45759.
- تشوي. رمز المرور ٤٥٧٥٩.
For Marshall, pass code 20112.
بالنسبة لمارشال، رمز المرور هو 20112.
- [Woman] Screen clearance. Stand by.
- [امرأة] شاشة واضحة. استعدوا.
Agent Choi, am I glad to see you.
العميل تشوي يسعدني رؤيتك.
Any new intel?
أي معلومات جديدة؟
- Well, we have two simultaneous attacks.
- حسنًا، لدينا هجومان متزامنان.
Don't know the body count yet.
لا أعرف عدد الجثث بعد.
The early estimates could be in the hundreds.
التقديرات الأولية قد تكون بالمئات.
We have a team tracking a possible remote detonation
لدينا فريق يتتبع احتمال حدوث تفجير عن بعد
from the City Hall attack.
من هجوم مبنى البلدية
Mercury 2?
عطارد 2؟
Airborne until we know more.
محمول جواً حتى نعرف المزيد
Are there any other agents in the house?
هل هناك أي وكلاء آخرين في المنزل؟
Yes.
نعم.
There's one from our unit.
هناك واحد من وحدتنا.
Two from Langley.
إثنان من لانجلي.
One from DoD
واحدة من وزارة الدفاع
and some trigger-happy son of a bitch from Homeland.
وبعض الأوغاد المتحمسين من الوطن.
- Don't tell any of them what you have.
- لا تخبر أحداً بما لديك.
We'll get a team to you soon.
سوف نرسل لك فريقًا قريبًا.
Stay strong, son.
ابقى قويا يا ابني.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
[tense music]
[موسيقى متوترة]
[music fades]
[تتلاشى الموسيقى]
[Choi sighs]
[تنهد تشوي]
[water splashing]
[رش الماء]
He seems fine.
يبدو أنه بخير.
Lucky it was CS, not sarin.
لحسن الحظ أنه كان غاز CS وليس غاز السارين.
How are you?
كيف حالك؟
A little better.
أفضل قليلا.
I should have been more diligent.
كان ينبغي لي أن أكون أكثر اجتهادًا.
- Hey. No one saw this coming.
- مهلا، لم يتوقع أحد هذا.
Don't beat yourself up.
لا تلوم نفسك.
Just follow protocol and we'll get out of this safely.
فقط اتبع البروتوكول وسوف نخرج من هذا بأمان.
[comms blaring]
[صوت الاتصالات الصاخب]
- [Marshall] Authorization for Safe House 5102.
- [مارشال] التفويض للبيت الآمن 5102.
- Tango Charlie Romeo Romeo Five.
- تانجو تشارلي روميو روميو فايف.
You're on speaker.
أنت على مكبر الصوت.
We currently have five guests in the house.
لدينا حاليا خمسة ضيوف في المنزل.
One agent's in recovery.
أحد الوكلاء في حالة تعافي.
- Housekeeper, can you repeat?
- مدبرة المنزل، هل يمكنك التكرار؟
Did you say five guests?
هل قلت خمسة ضيوف؟
[Anderson] Yes, sir.
[أندرسون] نعم سيدي.
- Agent Choi here. Is there any intel on
- العميل تشوي هنا. هل هناك أي معلومات استخباراتية؟
when the shelter in place order will be lifted?
متى سيتم رفع أمر البقاء في المكان ؟
- [Marshall] All agents are to follow protocol.
- [مارشال] يجب على جميع الوكلاء اتباع البروتوكول.
Everyone?
الجميع؟
- All agents are to follow protocol.
- يجب على جميع الوكلاء إتباع البروتوكول.
Command, this is Halton.
أمر، هذا هالتون.
I'm running point.
أنا أركض نقطة.
Is there any indication when the order will be lifted?
هل هناك أي مؤشر على موعد رفع الأمر؟
[Marshall] No, none.
[مارشال] لا، لا يوجد.
LAPD and the National Guard are mobilized evacuating
شرطة لوس أنجلوس تم تعبئة الحرس الوطني للإخلاء
a two-mile radius of the affected area as we speak.
دائرة نصف قطرها ميلين من المنطقة المتضررة كما نتحدث
- So you're saying we're stuck here.
- إذن أنت تقول أننا عالقون هنا.
[Marshall] That's affirmative.
[مارشال] هذا إيجابي.
That's fucking great.
هذا رائع للغاية.
- Halton, can you pick up the handset?
- هالتون، هل يمكنك التقاط سماعة الهاتف؟
We have new intel we need to discuss.
لدينا معلومات جديدة نحتاج إلى مناقشتها.
I'm here.
أنا هنا.
Can you say that again?
هل يمكنك أن تقول ذلك مرة أخرى؟
Command, that is highly--
الأمر، هذا هو للغاية-
[electronics flickering, shutting down]
[وميض الأجهزة الإلكترونية وإغلاقها]
Command?
يأمر؟
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
System override.
تجاوز النظام.
It's a remote lockdown.
إنه إغلاق عن بعد.
They're locking us in here.
إنهم يحبسوننا هنا.
[Sorello] Fuck. Go.
[سوريلو] اللعنة. اذهب.
[Anderson] Get to the door!
[أندرسون] اذهب إلى الباب!
It's the door.
إنه الباب
- [Sorello] Go. Come on. Pull. Pull.
- [سوريلو] انطلق. هيا.</ i> اسحب. اسحب.
[both straining]
[كلاهما متوتر]
They cut the power.
لقد قطعوا الكهرباء.
The door's locked.
الباب مغلق.
There's no way in or out.
لا يوجد طريق للدخول أو الخروج.
- [Owens] Ugh! - [Sorello] Shit.
- [أوينز] أوه! - [سوريلو] يا إلهي.
What did he say?
ماذا قال؟
- How do we lose power if some of these lights are still up?
- كيف نفقد الطاقة إذا كانت بعض هذه الأضواء لا تزال مضاءة؟
Battery backups.
نسخ احتياطية للبطارية.
Doesn't take much to power a bulb.
لا يتطلب الأمر الكثير لتشغيل المصباح.
- Any other exits? - It's a safe house.
- هل هناك أي مخرج آخر؟ - إنه منزل آمن.
How many exits you think it's gonna have?
كم عدد المخارج التي تعتقد أنها ستكون موجودة؟
[disconnected beeping]
[صوت صفير منقطع]
[Owens] There's no signal.
[أوينز] لا توجد إشارة.
They jammed it.
لقد قاموا بتشويشه.
Fucking protocol.
بروتوكول سخيف.
- It's like they think we're the enemy.
- يبدو أنهم يعتقدون أننا العدو.
They think we're the enemy.
يعتقدون أننا العدو.
What the fuck does that mean?
ماذا يعني هذا اللعنة؟
- Command traced the detonator signal
- تتبعت القيادة إشارة المفجر
from today's attacks to here.
من هجمات اليوم إلى هنا.
They think one of us is the bomber.
يظنون أن واحداً منا هو المفجر.
Wait, wait.
انتظر، انتظر.
Why would the bomber keep the detonator on them?
لماذا يحتفظ المفجر بالمفجر عليه؟
To set off the next bomb.
لتفجير القنبلة التالية.
- [Halton] We're all detained until one of us surrenders.
- [هالتون] سنُحتجز جميعًا حتى يستسلم أحدنا.
You believe that?
هل تصدق ذلك؟
They traced the signal here.
لقد تتبعوا الإشارة هنا.
Well, I was shot at.
حسنًا، لقد تم إطلاق النار علي.
Yeah, so were we.
نعم، كنا كذلك.
I've been here the whole time.
لقد كنت هنا طوال الوقت.
You can-- you can check the cameras.
يمكنك-- يمكنك التحقق من الكاميرات.
- That's pretty convenient for you, ain't it?
- هذا مناسب جدًا لك، أليس كذلك؟
The power's out, so we can't check them, can we?
لقد انقطعت الكهرباء، لذلك لا يمكننا التحقق منهم، أليس كذلك؟
- I'm just putting my cards on the table, too.
- أنا فقط أضع أوراقي على الطاولة أيضًا.
- And maybe that's something we should all do.
- وربما هذا هو الشيء الذي ينبغي علينا جميعا أن نفعله.
What the fuck were you on the line about?
ما الذي كنت على الخط بشأنه؟
- No, that's above your pay grade.
- لا، هذا فوق مستوى راتبك.
You're hiding something.
أنت تخفي شيئا ما.
That's my business, not yours.
هذا شأني، وليس شأنك.
- Look, they said the detonator is still here.
- انظر، لقد قالوا أن المفجر لا يزال هنا.
I mean, we can search the place, right?
أعني، يمكننا البحث في المكان، أليس كذلك؟
- Detonator could be the size of a dime.
- يمكن أن يكون حجم المفجر بحجم العملة المعدنية عشرة سنتات.
- Yeah, and where does that leave us?
- نعم، وأين يتركنا هذا؟
[Choi] I don't know.
[تشوي] لا أعرف.
You want to start shooting folks?
هل تريد أن تبدأ في إطلاق النار على الناس؟
- Start with him. - Oh.
- ابدأ معه. - أوه.
No, you do not want to be pushing my buttons right now.
لا، أنت لا تريد أن تضغط على أزرارى الآن.
You are hiding something,
أنت تخفي شيئا ما
and we deserve to know what it is before we get killed.
ونحن نستحق أن نعرف ما هو قبل أن نقتل.
- Trust me, if I was the enemy, you would all be dead by now.
- صدقني، لو كنت العدو، لكنتم جميعا ميتين الآن.
I miss anything?
هل افتقد شيئا؟
[gun cocks]
[ديوك البندقية]
[Halton] Choi.
[هالتون] تشوي
Like I said.
كما قلت.
- I don't want to catch anybody in a room alone.
- لا أريد أن أجعل أي شخص في غرفة بمفرده.
Got it?
فهمتها؟
[tense music]
[موسيقى متوترة]
- No terror group has claimed responsibility
- لم تعلن أي جماعة إرهابية مسؤوليتها عن الهجوم
for these well-coordinated, precisely calculated attacks.
لهذه الهجمات المنسقة جيدًا والمحسوبة بدقة
First responders on the scene have confirmed
أكد المستجيبون الأوائل في مكان الحادث
that a chemical agent was used at the City Hall attack.
أن مادة كيميائية استخدمت في الهجوم على مبنى البلدية.
Across the street,
عبر الشارع
I am seeing officers getting suited up in hazmat suits,
أرى ضباطًا يرتدون بدلات الحماية من المواد الخطرة،
- [TV host] and multiple bomb squads have been dispatched
- [مقدم البرامج التلفزيونية] وتم إرسال فرق متعددة لتفكيك القنابل
to continue looking for more devices.
للاستمرار في البحث عن المزيد من الأجهزة.
Police are sifting through the aftermath and searching
تقوم الشرطة بالتنقيب في أعقاب الحادث والبحث
for any additional explosives.
لأي متفجرات إضافية.
[helicopters rotors whirring]
[دوي دوارات المروحيات]
- [Owens] Your pupils look better.
- [أوينز] تبدو حدقات عينيك أفضل.
Ahh. Yeah.
اه. نعم.
Everything's still blurry, though.
لا يزال كل شيء غامضًا، رغم ذلك.
Look, this is nuts.
انظر، هذا مجنون.
We're under a shelter in place order from a WMD thread.
نحن تحت أمر البقاء في المنزل بسبب موضوع أسلحة الدمار الشامل.
We've got no power.
ليس لدينا أي قوة.
Yeah, we're screwed here.
نعم، نحن في ورطة هنا.
What do you remember?
ماذا تتذكر؟
I remember waking up.
أتذكر أنني استيقظت.
And both of us being nervous about this assignment.
وكنا كلينا متوترين بشأن هذه المهمة.
The quiet ride to Mercury 2.
الرحلة الهادئة إلى ميركوري 2
And then I remember you taking a phone call
ثم أتذكر أنك تلقيت مكالمة هاتفية
and splitting away from the group.
والانفصال عن المجموعة
And then...
وبعد ذلك...
I turned around and gas was just spraying everywhere.
استدرت وكان الغاز يتناثر في كل مكان.
[rapid gunfire]
[إطلاق نار سريع]
Then everything else is just a blur.
ثم كل شيء آخر هو مجرد ضبابية.
But I remember your voice.
ولكنني أتذكر صوتك
- [Owens] Come on, Reeves. Let's go.
- [أوينز] تعال يا ريفز، دعنا نذهب .
I got you.
لقد حصلت عليك
[Reeves grunting]
[ريفز يئن]
And then we were here.
وبعد ذلك كنا هنا.
I could have lost you.
كان من الممكن أن أفقدك.
Hey, I'm alive.
مهلا، أنا على قيد الحياة.
I'm here, and you're here.
أنا هنا، وأنت هنا.
You still a fighter?
هل مازلت مقاتلا؟
Always.
دائماً.
You still got it?
هل لا تزال حصلت عليه؟
- Hey. Halton wanted me to tell--
- مهلاً. أراد هالتون مني أن أخبرك...
Yeah.
نعم.
Yeah. I kept it safe.
نعم، لقد أبقيته آمنًا.
- Okay. That was a targeted attack,
- حسنًا. كان ذلك هجومًا مُستهدفًا.
which means they must have known why we were there.
وهذا يعني أنهم لابد وأن عرفوا سبب وجودنا هناك.
It was classified.
لقد تم تصنيفه.
- [Reeves] We gotta tell the others.
- [ريفز] علينا أن نخبر الآخرين.
No.
لا.
- Hey. Hey. I know it's dangerous.
- هيه، هيه، أعلم أن الأمر خطير.
Are you sure?
هل أنت متأكد؟
[sighs] No. Not at all.
[تنهد] لا، على الإطلاق.
But if we are being hunted,
ولكن إذا كنا نتعرض للمطاردة،
then we're gonna need allies in the room.
إذن سنحتاج إلى حلفاء في الغرفة.
God forbid this gets any worse.
لا سمح الله أن يسوء هذا الأمر أكثر من ذلك.
We both nearly died today.
لقد كدنا أن نموت اليوم.
Me too.
أنا أيضاً.
- I know we're all under suspicion.
- أعلم أننا جميعًا تحت الشك.
This is my first time back in the field after three years.
هذه هي المرة الأولى التي أعود فيها إلى الميدان بعد ثلاث سنوات.
I work in development,
أنا أعمل في مجال التطوير،
at the Department of Defense Special Projects.
في مشاريع خاصة بوزارة الدفاع .
The what?
ماذا؟
It's the DoD creative arm.
إنه الذراع الإبداعي لوزارة الدفاع.
- I'm a developer, and Reeves
- أنا مطور، وريفز
is my associate in the Secret Service.
هو زميلي في الخدمة السرية.
So you're Q and he's Bond.
إذن أنت Q وهو بوند.
- We've been working together for the past nine months
- لقد عملنا معًا خلال الأشهر التسعة الماضية
on a new assignment.
في مهمة جديدة.
We were here in Los Angeles to deliver it to Mercury 2.
لقد كنا هنا في لوس أنجلوس لتسليمها إلى ميركوري 2.
- [Choi] That's why you were outside City Hall?
- [تشوي] لهذا السبب كنت خارج مبنى البلدية؟
- We were to deliver special project
- كان علينا تقديم مشروع خاص
code name C49.
الاسم الرمزي C49.
The case got damaged.
لقد تعرضت القضية للضرر.
- What is that? A monocular?
- ما هذا؟ أحادي العين؟
- This one can only be activated by my ID.
- لا يمكن تفعيل هذا إلا عن طريق معرفي.
One of my eyes.
إحدى عيني.
We were to deliver it today to the Mercury 2.
كان من المقرر أن نسلمه اليوم إلى ميركوري 2.
To lock it to him.
لقفلها عليه.
- It's got a built-in fail-safe in case the subject dies too.
- تم تزويده بنظام أمان مدمج في حالة وفاة الشخص أيضًا.
- If I were dead, this device would recognize
- لو كنت ميتًا، فإن هذا الجهاز سوف يتعرف علي
that my pupils were mid-dilated.
أن حدقتي كانت متوسعة في المنتصف.
Cadaveric position.
وضع الجثة.
- So it's a device that protects itself,
- إذن فهو جهاز يحمي نفسه،
but not the user.
ولكن ليس المستخدم.
What the hell does it do?
ماذا يفعل هذا الجحيم؟
- We're not authorized-- - Bullshit. What the hell--
- لسنا مُصرّحين-- - كلام فارغ. ماذا بحق الجحيم--
- We're not authorized to reveal that.
- ليس لدينا الحق في الكشف عن ذلك.
But if this is what they're after,
ولكن إذا كان هذا هو ما يبحثون عنه،
we're gonna need your help to keep it safe.
سنحتاج إلى مساعدتك للحفاظ عليه آمنًا.
- This device stays between me and Reeves
- هذا الجهاز يبقى بيني وبين ريفز
and no one else.
ولا أحد غيره.
[Reeves coughs]
[ريفز يسعل]
[Owens] That went well.
[أوينز] لقد سار الأمر على ما يرام.
We had to withhold some things.
لقد كان علينا أن نمتنع عن بعض الأشياء.
That's the business.
هذا هو العمل.
We told them enough to get them off our backs.
لقد أخبرناهم بما يكفي لإبعادهم عن ظهورنا.
(coughs) Yeah.
(السعال) نعم.
I'm okay.
انا بخير.
Go keep an eye on them,
اذهب وراقبهم
especially that prick from Homeland.
وخاصة ذلك الأحمق من الوطن.
[sniggers]
[ضحكات مكتومة]
[water pouring]
[سكب الماء]
- It's time for you to level with me.
- لقد حان الوقت لكي تكون صريحًا معي.
- Listen, I appreciate our past.
- اسمع، أنا أقدر ماضينا.
- I do. - Appreciate it?
- انا افعل. - أقدر ذلك؟
You need to remember it.
يجب عليك أن تتذكره.
I ran the Moscow corridor when you were still pretty new.
لقد قمت بإدارة ممر موسكو عندما كنت لا تزال جديدًا إلى حد ما.
I extracted a Soviet asset to this same safe house.
لقد قمت باستخراج أحد الأصول السوفيتية إلى نفس المنزل الآمن.
Everyone's day is going to get a lot more complicated
سيصبح يوم الجميع أكثر تعقيدًا
if we don't work together.
إذا لم نعمل معًا.
Do you have a question, Halton?
هل لديك سؤال، هالتون؟
- Choi, if I were you, I would not make me the enemy.
- تشوي، لو كنت مكانك، فلن أجعل نفسي عدوًا.
You're going to get us all killed.
سوف تتسبب في قتلنا جميعا.
I'm trying to save you all.
أحاول إنقاذكم جميعا.
God damn it, Choi.
لعنة الله عليك يا تشوي.
What's the problem?
ما هي المشكلة؟
He finally tell you he's working with the North Koreans?
وأخيرًا أخبرك أنه يعمل مع الكوريين الشماليين؟
Yeah.
نعم.
- I'm Chinese American, you fucking idiot.
- أنا أمريكي صيني، أيها الأحمق اللعين.
- Doesn't make me feel any better.
- لا يجعلني أشعر بتحسن.
Hey, come on, Sorello.
مهلا، هيا، سوريلو.
No, it's fine.
لا، إنه بخير.
You want to do this? We could do this.
هل تريد أن تفعل هذا؟ يمكننا أن نفعل هذا.
- Yeah, I'd love to. - Yeah?
- نعم، أود ذلك. - نعم؟
You paranoid fuck.
أيها الأحمق المصاب بجنون العظمة.
In this house, you are the bottom of the food chain.
في هذا البيت، أنت في أسفل السلسلة الغذائية.
Nobody here knows who the fuck you are,
لا أحد هنا يعرف من أنت،
- why you're here, - I have every right to know
- لماذا أنت هنا؟ - لدي كل الحق في معرفة ذلك.
- You could be some-- - what's going on here.
- قد تكون بعض-- - ما يحدث هنا.
In fact, it's my job to know.
في الواقع، من واجبي أن أعرف.
And if you think for one second that I'm gonna wait
وإذا كنت تعتقد ولو لثانية واحدة أنني سأنتظر
until someone shoots me in the back of the fucking head
حتى أطلق أحدهم النار على مؤخرة رأسي اللعين
over whatever it is that you're keeping secret,
على أي شيء تخفيه سراً،
you got another think coming.
لقد حصلت على فكرة أخرى قادمة.
- I can guarantee you, no one will shoot you
- أستطيع أن أضمن لك أنه لن يطلق عليك أحد النار
in the back of the head.
في مؤخرة الرأس.
- This isn't the time to be holding back intel.
- هذا ليس الوقت المناسب لإخفاء المعلومات الاستخباراتية.
- It's not the time to be sharing intel either.
- ليس هذا هو الوقت المناسب لمشاركة المعلومات أيضًا.
I gave you your one warning earlier.
لقد أعطيتك تحذيرك الوحيد في وقت سابق.
- [Sorello] And this is your warning.
- [سوريلو] وهذا هو تحذيرك.
- [Choi] Yeah? - Guys.
- [تشوي] نعم؟ - يا شباب.
Come clean now.
تعال نظيفا الآن.
There's someone at the window!
هناك شخص ما عند النافذة!
[loud explosion]
[انفجار قوي]
[tense music]
[موسيقى متوترة]
[rapid gunfire]
[إطلاق نار سريع]
- [Gunman Six] Cover. - [Gunman Seven] Go!
- [Gunman Six] غلاف - [Gunman Seven] انطلق!
[glass shatters]
[تحطم الزجاج]
[Choi] Shit.
[تشوي] يا إلهي
[Reeves] Owens, move!
[ريفز] أوينز، تحرك!
[overlapping grunting]
[تذمر متداخل]
[intense music]
[موسيقى مكثفة]
[Choi] No, no.
[تشوي] لا، لا.
Bridge, bridge.
جسر، جسر.
[glass shatters]
[تحطم الزجاج]
[knife clanking]
[صوت طعن السكين]
[Gunman choking]
[مسلح يختنق]
- [bone cracks] - [Gunman grunts]
- [تشققات العظام] - [يصرخ الرجل المسلح]
[beeping]
[صوت صفير]
[bomb explodes]
[تنفجر القنبلة]
[high-pitched ringing]
[رنين عالي النبرة]
[muffled grunting]
[خرخرة مكتومة]
Mag.
مجلة
[Reeves] Get down.
[ريفز] انزل.
- [Reeves] [Indistinct], watch out.
- [ريفز] [غير واضح]، احترس.
Reeves. Reeves.
ريفز. ريفز.
Come on.
تعال.
No, no, look at me.
لا، لا، انظر إلي.
Look at me, please.
أنظر إلي من فضلك.
No, no, no, no. No, no.
لا، لا، لا، لا. لا، لا.
Come on.
تعال.
Oh, my...come on.
أوه، يا إلهي... هيا.
Don't leave me.
لا تتركنى.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Clear.
واضح.
[rapid gunfire]
[إطلاق نار سريع]
[gunman screaming]
[صراخ المسلح]
[crash]
[يتحطم]
Now we're clear.
الآن أصبحنا واضحين.
[loud explosion]
[انفجار قوي]
Oh.
أوه.
What the hell was that?
ماذا كان هذا بحق الجحيم؟
[pensive music]
[موسيقى تأملية]
- Can we get a sheet for him or something?
- هل يمكننا الحصول على ورقة له أو شيء من هذا القبيل؟
[Choi] The ropes are gone.
[تشوي] الحبال ذهبت.
That's how they got away.
بهذه الطريقة تمكنوا من الفرار
Hey. In here.
مرحبا. هنا.
- Oh, come on. How did this happen?
- أوه، هيا. كيف حدث هذا؟
- [Halton] I shot the guy in the head.
- [هالتون] لقد أطلقت النار على الرجل في رأسه.
He must have blown up.
يجب أن يكون قد انفجر.
- [Sorello] The guy that Choi chucked out the window,
- [سوريلو] الرجل الذي ألقاه تشوي من النافذة،
he exploded too.
لقد انفجر أيضًا
- [Anderson] And the other one escaped.
- [أندرسون] والآخر هرب
[pensive music]
[موسيقى تأملية]
[Garcia] RPG! Watch out.
[غارسيا] لعبة تقمص أدوار! انتبه.
Incoming.
وارد.
[muffled gunfire, indistinct shouting]
[إطلاق نار مكتوم، صراخ غير واضح]
[Garcia] Exit fire!
[غارسيا] الخروج من النار!
[Owens] Context right.
[أوينز] السياق صحيح.
[Garcia] Move it. Move it.
[غارسيا] تحرك. تحرك.
Cover me.
غطني
[Owens] Garcia!
[أوينز] جارسيا
[indistinct shout]
[صراخ غير واضح]
[Owens] Ugh, I'm hit!
[أوينز] آه، لقد أصبت!
[Owens crying]
[أوينز يبكي]
- You know what I'm trying to figure out?
- هل تعلم ما أحاول اكتشافه؟
If one of us is the bomber,
إذا كان أحدنا هو المفجر،
then why were we just attacked?
فلماذا تم مهاجمتنا إذن؟
How is that thing still on?
كيف لا يزال هذا الشيء موجودا؟
It's got a backup battery.
لقد حصلت على بطارية احتياطية.
- Lot of medicine inside. Keeps it fresh.
- الكثير من الأدوية بالداخل. يُبقيها طازجة.
- Medicine? You got quick clot in here?
- طب؟ عندك جلطة سريعة هنا؟
[Anderson] Yeah.
[أندرسون] نعم.
The left-hand side.
الجانب الأيسر
- I thought these windows were bulletproof.
- اعتقدت أن هذه النوافذ مضادة للرصاص.
- Bulletproof, not explosive proof.
- مضاد للرصاص، وليس مضاد للانفجار.
Never seen the street so empty.
لم أرى الشارع فارغًا هكذا من قبل.
- Yeah, that's what happens when you evacuate a city.
- نعم، هذا ما يحدث عندما يتم إخلاء المدينة.
- [Announcer] Downtown Los Angeles has been evacuated.
- [المذيع] تم إخلاء وسط مدينة لوس أنجلوس
[helicopter whirring]
[هدير المروحية]
- [Announcer] [indistinct] Downtown jurisdiction.
- [المذيع] [غير واضح] سلطة وسط المدينة.
- [News Anchor] By order of the governor,
- [مذيع الأخبار] بأمر من المحافظ،
martial law has been declared
تم إعلان الأحكام العرفية
for Los Angeles and its surrounding cities.
لوس أنجلوس والمدن المحيطة بها
With risk of any ongoing threats and use of chemical weapons,
مع وجود خطر من أي تهديدات مستمرة واستخدام الأسلحة الكيميائية،
it has become a quarantine zone.
لقد أصبحت منطقة حجر صحي.
To ensure safety,
لضمان السلامة
all residents in the immediate and surrounding areas
جميع المقيمين في المناطق المجاورة والمناطق المجاورة
have been successfully evacuated
تم إخلاؤهم بنجاح
while the investigation continues.
بينما يستمر التحقيق .
[somber music]
[موسيقى حزينة]
- Are you sure you want to do that?
- هل أنت متأكد أنك تريد القيام بذلك؟
- He hasn't blown up yet. I reckon we'll be fine.
- لم ينفجر بعد. أعتقد أننا سنكون بخير.
BOOM!
بوم!
They don't even bother hiding their faces.
إنهم لا يكلفون أنفسهم عناء إخفاء وجوههم.
- When you're wearing a dead trigger,
- عندما ترتدي زنادًا ميتًا،
it doesn't matter who sees you.
لا يهم من يراك.
Anyone recognize him?
هل أحد يتعرف عليه؟
He's dead.
لقد مات.
Why did he not explode?
لماذا لم ينفجر؟
- [Halton] The trigger mechanism is toast.
- [هالتون] آلية الزناد محترقة.
- This is some guerrilla warfare shit.
- هذا هو بعض حرب العصابات القرف.
The moment his heart stops, boom.
في اللحظة التي يتوقف فيها قلبه، بوم.
Anything on him?
هل هناك أي شيء عنه؟
He's clean.
إنه نظيف.
Minus, of course, the block of C4 up his ass.
باستثناء، بالطبع، كتلة C4 في مؤخرته.
- You see anything on that tablet?
- هل ترى أي شيء على هذا اللوح؟
- I don't remember. It all happened so fast, and...
- لا أتذكر. حدث كل شيء بسرعة، و...
- You work in development, and the best you've got is,
- أنت تعمل في مجال التطوير، وأفضل ما لديك هو،
"I don't know, it all happened so--"
"لا أعلم، لقد حدث كل شيء هكذا-"
- There were explosions, so forgive me
- كانت هناك انفجارات، لذا سامحني
if I'm a little fuzzy on the details.
إذا كنت غامضًا بعض الشيء بشأن التفاصيل.
- Those details got your partner killed.
- هذه التفاصيل أدت إلى مقتل شريكك.
Fuck you, Choi!
اذهب إلى الجحيم يا تشوي!
I'm not the one holding back intel.
أنا لست الشخص الذي يحجب المعلومات.
They seem more interested in you.
يبدو أنهم مهتمون بك أكثر.
- Hey, hey. Hey, hey, hey.
- هي، هي. هي، هي، هي.
Don't!
لا!
You don't want to do that.
أنت لا تريد أن تفعل ذلك.
- Just let her go, man. - Stay out of this.
- دعها تذهب، يا رجل. - ابق بعيدًا عن هذا.
- Okay. I'm just saying,
- حسنًا. أنا فقط أقول،
that the only way we're gonna get through this
هذه هي الطريقة الوحيدة التي سنتمكن بها من تجاوز هذا الأمر
is if we work together.
إذا عملنا معًا.
- One more fucking move, I dare you.
- حركة أخرى سخيفة، أتحداك.
- I fucking-- - Choi, let him up!
- أنا اللعين-- - تشوي، دعه ينهض!
- dare you. - [gunshot]
- أتحداك. - [طلقة نارية]
- That was my last warning to everyone here.
- كان هذا تحذيري الأخير للجميع هنا.
[Anderson winces]
[أندرسون يتألم]
Don't be such a pussy.
لا تكن مثل هذا الجبان.
- I'm not. - Well, let me finish.
- أنا لست كذلك. - حسنًا، دعني أنهي.
- I'm sorry... about your partner.
- أنا آسف... بشأن شريكك.
- [Owens] I wish I could have done more.
- [أوينز] أتمنى أن أكون قد فعلت المزيد.
- Is that the first time you lost someone?
- هل هذه هي المرة الأولى التي تفقد فيها شخصًا ما؟
- I served a tour in Iraq before I joined the DoD.
- لقد خدمت في العراق قبل انضمامي إلى وزارة الدفاع.
Put my degree to use.
استخدم شهادتي.
You serve too?
هل تخدم أيضا؟
The Marines.
مشاة البحرية.
- How the hell did you get away with that?
- كيف تمكنت من فعل ذلك؟
Don't ask.
لا تسأل.
Rangers.
رينجرز.
No shit.
لا القرف.
For a while, anyway.
لفترة من الوقت على أية حال.
I was in Iraq, and my platoon was hit with an IED.
كنت في العراق، وتعرضت فصيلتي لانفجار عبوة ناسفة.
Same old crap. You've heard it before.
نفس الكلام القديم. سمعته من قبل.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
- Well, our convoy was blown to shit,
- حسنًا، لقد تحطمت موكبنا تمامًا،
and my second gunner,
ومدفعي الثاني
Garcia,
جارسيا،
I see him out the window of the Humvee,
أراه من نافذة سيارة الهمفي،
and he's what, 100 yards away,
وهو على بعد 100 ياردة،
and he's down.
وهو في الأسفل.
So I left the convoy,
فتركت القافلة
and I almost get to Garcia,
وأنا تقريبا وصلت إلى جارسيا،
and then suddenly I feel this burning in the side of my--
ثم فجأة أشعر بهذا الحرق في جانبي--
You all right?
هل انت بخير؟
I blacked out.
لقد فقدت الوعي.
I thought I was dead.
اعتقدت أنني ميت.
A passing convoy came by and saved us.
لقد مر موكب عابر وأنقذنا.
God, I couldn't save him.
يا إلهي لم أستطع إنقاذه.
You can't save everyone.
لا يمكنك انقاذ الجميع .
I lost my sister, too.
لقد فقدت أختي أيضًا.
[somber music]
[موسيقى حزينة]
- When I came back, I had the usual. Nightmares...
- عندما عدت، كان لديّ كالمعتاد. كوابيس...
shortness of breath... the thoughts...
ضيق في التنفس... الأفكار...
Then I started working in development tech
ثم بدأت العمل في مجال تكنولوجيا التطوير
and I found a way to busy my mind.
ووجدت طريقة لإشغال ذهني.
Busy my...
مشغول يا...
You found a new passion.
لقد وجدت شغفًا جديدًا.
- I found something where I could save lives,
- لقد وجدت شيئًا حيث يمكنني إنقاذ الأرواح،
even my own.
حتى خاصتي.
[loud alarm blaring]
[صوت إنذار عالي]
- [Owens] What the hell is that?
- [أوينز] ما هذا بحق الجحيم؟
[Anderson] Go.
[أندرسون] اذهب
Holding room! Go!
غرفة الانتظار! اذهب!
[all grunting]
[جميع الأنين]
[Sorello] Oh, shit.
[سوريلو] أوه، اللعنة.
Okay, they must've hacked into the system.
حسنًا، لا بد أنهم اخترقوا النظام.
[Halton] Why?
[هالتون] لماذا؟
What does that accomplish?
ماذا يحقق ذلك؟
- Corner us to force us to move.
- يحاصروننا لإجبارنا على التحرك.
I mean, look at where we are.
أعني، انظر إلى أين نحن.
- We're fish in a... - Barrel.
- نحن سمكة في... - برميل.
[explosion]
[انفجار]
[Sorello] What is that?
[سوريلو] ما هذا؟
[tense music]
[موسيقى متوترة]
[Halton] Get back.
[هالتون] ارجع
[clatter of falling debris]
[صوت الحطام المتساقط]
[Owens] Storage room.
[أوينز] غرفة التخزين
It's screener smoke.
إنه دخان الشاشة.
- Gotta move. Cover your mouth.
- يجب أن تتحرك. غطِّ فمك.
[Choi] Owens, come on.
[تشوي] أوينز، تعال.
- [Owens] Cover the door . - [Choi] Let's go.
- [أوينز] قم بتغطية الباب . - [تشوي] لنذهب.
I'll take the right flank.
سأتخذ الجانب الأيمن.
Anderson, wait.
أندرسون، انتظر.
Got you.
لقد حصلت عليك
[Owens straining]
[أوينز يجهد]
[gunshots]
[طلقات نارية]
[Sorello groans]
[تأوهات الأخ]
Oh, Jesus!
يا يسوع!
[Anderson] Halton.
[أندرسون] هالتون.
[automatic gunfire]
[إطلاق نار أوتوماتيكي]
[Sorello groaning]
[الأخ المتأوه]
[bomb beeping]
[صوت قنبلة]
[explosion]
[انفجار]
[Anderson grunts]
[أندرسون يئن]
[grunting and groaning]
[تذمر وتأوه]
[metal clanking]
[صوت رنين معدني]
He's alive.
إنه على قيد الحياة.
Any explosives?
أي متفجرات؟
[Anderson] All clear.
[أندرسون] كل شيء واضح.
Cuff him.
قيدوه.
[Halton] Let's check the place.
[هالتون] دعونا نتحقق من المكان.
They might still be here.
ربما لا زالوا هنا.
You okay?
هل انت بخير؟
Yeah.
نعم.
Here.
هنا
[Sorello gasps]
[يتنفس سوريلو الصعداء]
[ominous music]
[موسيقى مشؤومة]
Where the fuck did they go?
أين ذهبوا بحق الجحيم؟
[Halton] In here.
[هالتون] هنا
[Choi] Shit.
[تشوي] يا إلهي
Give you a boost?
هل تعطيك دفعة؟
I'll go.
سأذهب.
Hold this.
امسك هذا.
Be careful.
احرص.
[Owens panting]
[أوينز يلهث]
Jesus, it's a trap.
يسوع، إنه فخ.
It's enough Semtex to bring down the whole building.
كمية كافية من مادة "سيمتكس" كافية لهدم المبنى بأكمله.
We're not getting out of here anytime soon.
لن نخرج من هنا في أي وقت قريب.
- Anderson, how the fuck could you not hear
- أندرسون، كيف لم تسمع؟
something happening right above your head?
هل يحدث شيء ما فوق رأسك مباشرة؟
Huh?
هاه؟
That's your job, to keep this place secure.
هذه مهمتك، أن تحافظ على هذا المكان آمنًا.
Exactly what is your job, Sorello?
ما هي وظيفتك بالضبط، سوريلو؟
You still haven't told us why you're even here.
لم تخبرنا بعد لماذا أنت هنا.
Homeland Security.
الأمن الداخلي.
It's my job to make sure that there's no terror threats
من واجبي التأكد من عدم وجود أي تهديدات إرهابية
on public transportation.
في وسائل النقل العام.
Oh well, that sure worked out for everyone.
حسنًا، هذا الأمر نجح مع الجميع بالتأكيد.
- The only one that knows anything is this asshole.
- الشخص الوحيد الذي يعرف أي شيء هو هذا الأحمق.
Let's wake him up and get some answers.
دعونا نوقظه ونحصل على بعض الإجابات.
- I want an agent posted at the window.
- أريد وكيلًا معينًا في النافذة.
Sorello, you're up.
أخي، لقد استيقظت.
Why me?
لماذا انا؟
Because you're the only one who will shoot first
لأنك الوحيد الذي سيطلق النار أولاً
and ask questions later.
وطرح الأسئلة لاحقًا.
[rhythmic, unsettling music]
[موسيقى إيقاعية ومزعجة]
Accelerant.
تسارع.
Don't worry. I'm only gonna give him a couple of ccs.
لا تقلق، سأعطيه بضع بطاقات ائتمان فقط.
More than enough to make him talk.
أكثر من كافي لجعله يتحدث.
What the fuck, Sorello?
ماذا بحق الجحيم، سوريلو؟
[Sorello] What?
[سوريلو] ماذا؟
- Anderson, you get on the windows.
- أندرسون، عليك أن تصعد إلى النوافذ.
Sorello, stay in here until he wakes up.
سوريلو، ابق هنا حتى يستيقظ.
- What am I, a babysitter now?
- ماذا أنا، جليسة أطفال الآن؟
- It's gonna be about five to 10 minutes.
- سوف يستغرق الأمر حوالي خمس إلى عشر دقائق.
Good.
جيد.
I want to speak to him first.
أريد أن أتحدث معه أولاً.
- Hey, Halton, this backup battery pack here.
- مرحبًا، هالتون، هذه حزمة البطارية الاحتياطية هنا.
I can remove it, right?
يمكنني إزالته، أليس كذلك؟
I guess so.
اعتقد ذلك.
- I think I can hook it up to the electrical system
- أعتقد أنني أستطيع توصيله بالنظام الكهربائي
in the supply room.
في غرفة الإمدادات.
Great idea, Owens.
فكرة رائعة، أوينز.
I'll see what I can do.
سأرى ما يمكنني فعله.
- You know what? My blood sugar's sinking.
- هل تعلم؟ مستوى السكر في دمي ينخفض.
Let me get some of this pizza right here.
دعني أحصل على بعض من هذه البيتزا هنا.
- It's a shame that bullet just nicked him.
- من العار أن الرصاصة أصابته للتو.
Can't believe you right now.
لا أستطيع أن أصدقك الآن.
- What? You want to order DoorDash or somethin'?
- ماذا؟ هل تريد طلب DoorDash أو شيء من هذا القبيل؟
Tell him to look for the guy on the sidewalk
اطلب منه أن يبحث عن الرجل على الرصيف
without a torso.
بدون جذع.
[tense music]
[موسيقى متوترة]
- [Halton] You've done this before.
- [هالتون] لقد فعلت هذا من قبل.
- Yeah, done a bit of electrical engineering
- نعم، قمت ببعض الهندسة الكهربائية
in my day.
في يومي.
[Sorello] Hey guys, he's awake.
[سوريلو] مرحبًا أيها الرجال، إنه مستيقظ.
[muttering]
[تمتمة]
Who are you?
من أنت؟
What's the matter?
ماذا جرى؟
You don't understand English?
أنت لا تفهم اللغة الإنجليزية؟
Hm?
هممم؟
Or maybe you just can't hear me?
أو ربما لا تستطيع سماعي؟
[speaks in Russian]
[يتحدث بالروسية]
[strains]
[سلالات]
Struggle all you want.
ناضل بقدر ما تريد.
You're not going anywhere.
أنت لا تذهب إلى أي مكان.
So you do understand me.
لذا فأنت تفهمني.
Can you speak?
هل تستطيع التكلم؟
Can you speak?!
هل تستطيع التكلم؟!
Maybe you'll talk a little easier with fewer teeth.
ربما ستتمكن من التحدث بشكل أسهل مع أسنان أقل.
Sorello.
أخ.
[groaning)}
[تأوه]
Who do you work for?
مع من تعمل؟
That's for all the people you killed today.
هذا لكل الأشخاص الذين قتلتهم اليوم.
This one's personal.
هذا أمر شخصي.
- [The operative screams in pain] - [bone snaps]
- [يصرخ العامل من الألم] - [ينكسر العظم]
[grunting]
[خرخرة]
[punch thrown]
[لكمة ألقيت]
- [Sorello] You want me to break the other one?
- [سوريلو] هل تريد مني أن أكسر الآخر؟
You got nine more, you fucking Russian fuck...
لديك تسعة أخرى، أيها الروسي اللعين...
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Don't test me.
لا تختبرني
I fucking dare you.
أنا أتحداك بشدة.
This is protocol?
هذا هو البروتوكول؟
Huh?
هاه؟
Are you just gonna let this happen?
هل ستسمح بحدوث هذا الأمر؟
[Choi] Oh, it's happening.
[تشوي] أوه، إنه يحدث.
[Sorello] Fucking cunt.
[سوريلو] لعنة المهبل.
I got a little something special for you.
لقد حصلت على شيء صغير خاص لك.
Owens, say something.
أوينز، قل شيئا.
Go back to your post.
العودة إلى مشاركاتك
- [Sorello] Who the fuck do you work for?
- [سوريلو] لمن تعمل بحق الجحيم؟
[panting]
[لهث]
Talk.
يتحدث.
- [screaming] - [Sorello] Whoo! Whoo!
- [يصرخ] - [سوريلو] هوو! هوو!
Come on!
تعالوا!
- We gotta be better than this.
-علينا أن نكون أفضل من هذا.
- When you're back in the field, you'll understand.
- عندما تعود إلى الميدان، سوف تفهم.
- I don't need to be in the field
- لا أحتاج إلى أن أكون في الميدان
to understand what's right and wrong.
لفهم ما هو الصواب والخطأ.
[taser clicking] [screaming]
[النقر بالمسدس الكهربائي] [الصراخ]
Talk!
يتحدث!
Can you feel that you fucking toast.
هل يمكنك أن تشعر بأنك تحمص؟
What are you hiding?
ماذا تخفي؟
Halton, let me in.
هالتون، اسمح لي بالدخول.
[Choi] No.
[تشوي] لا.
- He's gonna kill him before we get any actual intel.
- سوف يقتله قبل أن نحصل على أي معلومات حقيقية.
[The operative grunting]
[الشخير العامل]
- [Sorello] Fucking die, you motherfucker.
- [سوريلو] مت أيها الوغد.
[taser clicking] [screaming]
[النقر بالمسدس الكهربائي] [الصراخ]
Fucking die!
يموت اللعين!
Sorello. Take a break.
سوريلو. خذ استراحة.
You want some more?
هل تريد المزيد؟
- She said, take a break, Sorello.
- قالت خذ قسطًا من الراحة، سوريلو.
He's real soft for you.
إنه لطيف جدًا معك.
[gulps, spits]
[يبتلع، يبصق]
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Nobody.
لا أحد.
Wrong answer.
إجابة خاطئة.
[screaming]
[صراخ]
She's the good cop.
إنها الشرطية الصالحة.
Okay. Okay.
حسناً. حسناً.
- My mission is my name. My name is mission.
- مهمتي هي اسمي. اسمي هو مهمتي.
What is your mission?
ما هي مهمتك؟
Any more planned attacks?
هل هناك المزيد من الهجمات المخطط لها؟
- You, Daniel Reeves, Agent Choi, Anderson,
- أنت، دانيال ريفز، العميل تشوي، أندرسون،
you are here for reason.
أنت هنا لسبب.
We couldn't finish what we started at City Hall.
لم نتمكن من إكمال ما بدأناه في مبنى البلدية.
We separate you here to contain you.
نحن نفصلك هنا لاحتوائها.
What's the American phrase?
ما هي العبارة الامريكية؟
Ah, yeah. You're fish in barrel.
آه، نعم. أنت سمكة في برميل.
[laughing]
[يضحك]
Even you, Mia Angelica Owens.
حتى أنت، ميا أنجليكا أوينز.
Thirty-two.
اثنان وثلاثون.
Weapon specialist,
متخصص في الأسلحة،
having fling with her partner, Daniel Reeves.
بعد علاقة عاطفية مع شريكها دانييل ريفز.
Spent nine months on this case only to watch your lover die.
قضيت تسعة أشهر في هذه القضية فقط لمشاهدة حبيبك يموت.
[screaming]
[صراخ]
Kill him.
اقتله
You won't tell me? Fine.
لن تخبرني؟ حسنًا.
How about I give you the full fucking dose?
ماذا عن أن أعطيك الجرعة الكاملة اللعينة؟
What are you planning?!
ماذا تخطط؟
[laughs] Planning.
[يضحك] التخطيط.
[laughs]
[يضحك]
Tell me!
أخبرني!
- Poor girl, it's already in motion.
- يا لها من فتاة مسكينة، إنها في الحركة بالفعل.
You'll be with your lover real soon.
سوف تكون مع حبيبك قريبا.
Motherfucker!
ابن الزانية!
This isn't about you.
هذا لا يتعلق بك.
This isn't about you!
هذا لا يتعلق بك!
Owens!
أوينز!
You don't need to do this.
لا تحتاج إلى القيام بهذا.
You can't save anyone.
لا يمكنك انقاذ اي شخص .
It's cyanide. It's cyanide!
إنه السيانيد. إنه السيانيد!
You're already dead.
لقد مت بالفعل.
What are you doing? Huh?
ماذا تفعل؟ هاه؟
He was gonna talk.
كان ينوي التحدث.
- [stammers] I was--
- [يتلعثم] كنت--
[Halton] He was talking.
[هالتون] كان يتحدث.
- [Anderson] Just trying to help.
- [أندرسون] أحاول فقط المساعدة.
Trying to help?
تحاول المساعدة؟
[bomb beeping]
[صوت قنبلة]
[Owens] Sorello, check him.
[أوينز] سوريلو، تحقق منه.
Holy shit. It's armed.
يا إلهي! إنه مُسلّح.
Anderson, you searched him.
أندرسون، لقد بحثت عنه.
- I must have been moving too fast.
- لابد أنني كنت أتحرك بسرعة كبيرة.
Everybody out! Now!
الجميع للخارج الآن!
[explosion]
[انفجار]
[all groan]
[الجميع يتأوهون]
[electricity crackles]
[طقطقة الكهرباء]
[glass shatters]
[تحطم الزجاج]
[all groaning]
[كل الأنين]
Okay. Okay.
حسناً. حسناً.
I know what's going on here.
أنا أعلم ما يحدث هنا.
I figured it out.
لقد اكتشفت ذلك.
I know who is working with them.
أنا أعرف من يعمل معهم.
[gun clicks]
[نقرات البندقية]
- Pu--put that away.
- بو-ضع ذلك بعيدًا.
- Why would you run in there just before she got him?
- لماذا ركضت إلى هناك قبل أن تحصل عليه؟
She was gonna kill him.
لقد كانت ستقتله.
- No, he was about to sing.
- لا، كان على وشك الغناء.
- You don't--you don't know that.
- أنت لا تعرف ذلك.
You don't know what she was gonna do.
أنت لا تعرف ماذا كانت تنوي أن تفعل.
- You. You're the one that searched his body.
- أنت. أنت الذي فتّش جسده.
All the other bodies blew up.
انفجرت جميع الأجساد الأخرى.
- You weren't supposed to be in that room.
- لم يكن من المفترض أن تتواجد في تلك الغرفة.
And you, the one that's all calm, clear-headed, and quiet,
وأنت، الذي هو هادئ، وواضح الذهن، وهادئ،
didn't hear what was going on right above your fucking head.
لم أسمع ما كان يحدث فوق رأسك اللعين مباشرة.
[gun clicks]
[نقرات البندقية]
Answer the question.
أجب على السؤال
Are you kidding me?
هل تمزح معي؟
We haven't heard a peep from them
لم نسمع منهم أي صوت
since they've been up there.
منذ أن كانوا هناك.
None of us have.
لا أحد منا لديه.
The Russian, he had you dead to rights in that snow cloud,
الروسي، لقد قتلك تمامًا في تلك السحابة الثلجية،
and I saved you.
وأنا أنقذتك.
You would be dead if it wasn't for me.
سوف تكون ميتا لو لم يكن لي.
That fucker stabbed me in the shoulder,
لقد طعنني ذلك الوغد في كتفي،
and you still don't trust me?
ومازلت لا تثق بي؟
[gun clicks]
[نقرات البندقية]
[Halton] Sorello, wait.
[هالتون] أخي، انتظر.
- [Sorello] I can't believe it took me this long
- [سوريلو] لا أصدق أن الأمر استغرق مني كل هذا الوقت
to figure all of this out.
لمعرفة كل هذا
- You're a fucking traitor. - [gun clicks]
- أنت خائن حقير. - [صوت نقرة البندقية]
Look.
ينظر.
My name is Nathan Anderson.
اسمي ناثان أندرسون.
I gave the warning that they were outside the window.
لقد أعطيتهم تحذيرًا بأنهم كانوا خارج النافذة.
I saved all of your lives.
لقد أنقذت حياتكم جميعا.
But every--everyone thinks that--that I'm the throwaway?
لكن الجميع يظنون أنني شخص مهمل؟
I'm the mistake?
أنا الخطأ؟
That's what happens, right?
هذا ما يحدث، أليس كذلك؟
When you're a vet, you just make some mistakes.
عندما تكون طبيبًا بيطريًا، فإنك ترتكب بعض الأخطاء.
You're so eager to shoot someone today?
هل أنت متشوق جدًا لإطلاق النار على شخص ما اليوم؟
Shoot me, motherfucker.
أطلق النار علي، أيها الوغد.
Shoot me!
اطلق النار علي!
- We're going to start establishing
- سوف نبدأ في التأسيس
some goddamn order here.
هناك بعض النظام اللعين هنا.
- First, Sorello, you're going to keep your gun
- أولاً، سوريلو، عليك أن تحتفظ بمسدسك
out of our faces.
من وجوهنا.
Second, Owens, take Anderson's gun.
ثانياً، أوينز، خذ مسدس أندرسون.
Take him upstairs and cuff him.
خذه إلى الطابق العلوي وقم بتقييده.
[Sorello sighs]
[تنهد الأخ]
- You don't have to do this, you know.
- ليس عليك القيام بهذا، كما تعلم.
We both lost people in the war.
لقد فقدنا كلانا أشخاصًا في الحرب.
I just couldn't handle it as well as you.
لم أستطع التعامل مع الأمر كما فعلت أنت.
Don't make this about me.
لا تجعل هذا الأمر يتعلق بي.
It's not.
ليست كذلك.
It's about them.
إن الأمر يتعلق بهم.
They die, but...
يموتون ولكن...
they stay with us.
إنهم يبقون معنا.
Their faces, their voices...
وجوههم، أصواتهم...
their last words.
كلماتهم الاخيرة.
They all stay with us.
كلهم يبقون معنا.
It's up to us to do better...
يتعين علينا أن نفعل ما هو أفضل...
for them.
من اجلهم.
Sorello was right.
وكان سوريلو على حق.
I nearly broke him.
لقد كاد أن يكسره.
- Choi. These terrorists, or whoever they are,
- تشوي. هؤلاء الإرهابيون، أو أيًا كانوا،
know more about us than we do. And all we know about them
يعرفون عنا أكثر مما نعرفه نحن. وكل ما نعرفه عنهم
is they're smuggling fucking bombs on their backs.
إنهم يقومون بتهريب القنابل اللعينة على ظهورهم.
It's time you told everyone what we're really dealing with.
لقد حان الوقت لتخبر الجميع بما نتعامل معه حقًا.
- People died today because--
- مات الناس اليوم بسبب-
- How many more people have to die
- كم عدد الأشخاص الذين يجب أن يموتوا ؟
before the end of this day?
قبل نهاية هذا اليوم؟
I'm not trying to find out.
أنا لا أحاول معرفة ذلك.
- You want to save lives? Start with us.
- هل تريد إنقاذ الأرواح؟ ابدأ معنا.
Tell them about the nukes.
أخبرهم عن الأسلحة النووية.
I fucking knew it.
لقد عرفت ذلك حقًا.
- Look, Reeves was right earlier.
- انظر، ريفز كان على حق في وقت سابق.
God forbid something happens to one of us.
لا سمح الله أن يحدث لأحدنا مكروه.
They're going to need to know what the hell is going on.
سوف يحتاجون إلى معرفة ما الذي يحدث.
Shit.
اللعنة.
There are two active footballs on this planet
هناك كرتان كرة قدم نشطتان على هذا الكوكب
that have direct operational access
التي لديها إمكانية الوصول التشغيلي المباشر
to America's nuclear arsenal.
إلى الترسانة النووية الأمريكية.
One of them is with POTUS,
واحد منهم مع POTUS،
the other with the vice president.
والآخر مع نائب الرئيس.
Earlier today, when our motorcade was attacked,
في وقت سابق من اليوم، عندما تعرض موكبنا للهجوم،
the Secret Service agent responsible for carrying this...
العميل السري المسؤول عن حمل هذا...
was killed,
تم قتله
and I took this from him to keep it safe.
وأخذت هذا منه للحفاظ عليه.
- I-is that-- is that what I think it is?
- هل هذا ما أعتقد أنه كذلك؟
- It functions as a mobile hub in our strategic defense system.
- يعمل كمركز متنقل في نظامنا الدفاعي الاستراتيجي.
[device beeps]
[صوت تنبيه الجهاز]
How operational are we talking?
ما مدى العمل الذي نتحدث عنه؟
- Launch, detonation, recall. All of it.
إطلاق، تفجير، استدعاء. كل شيء.
I mean, technically, we can win World War Three
أعني، من الناحية الفنية، يمكننا الفوز في الحرب العالمية الثالثة
from our couch.
من أريكتنا.
- What are all those little red dots?
- ما كل تلك النقاط الحمراء الصغيرة؟
- [Choi] Locations of every missile silo in America.
- [تشوي] مواقع كل مستودعات الصواريخ في أمريكا.
- Okay, but we have safeguards, right?
- حسنًا، ولكن لدينا ضمانات، أليس كذلك؟
Gold codes.
الرموز الذهبية.
- Do you wanna know what the hell this thing does?
- هل تريد أن تعرف ماذا يفعل هذا الشيء؟
[scanner beeps]
[أصوات تنبيه الماسح الضوئي]
- It generates gold codes. - Are you serious?
- يقوم بتوليد أكواد ذهبية. - هل أنت جاد؟
I'm not even trained to carry this thing.
أنا لست مدربًا حتى على حمل هذا الشيء.
- You were right to hide it today.
- لقد كنت على حق عندما أخفيت ذلك اليوم.
- Why should we trust either of you?
- لماذا يجب علينا أن نثق في أي منكما؟
- They must have known Reeves and I
- لا بد أنهم عرفوا ريفز وأنا
were supposed to deliver this to the VP today.
وكان من المفترض أن نسلم هذا إلى نائب الرئيس اليوم.
And when they failed, they used our own backup protocol
وعندما فشلوا، استخدموا بروتوكول النسخ الاحتياطي الخاص بنا
against us to trap us here.
ضدنا ليحاصرونا هنا.
None of this was a coincidence.
لم يكن كل هذا مصادفة.
They've been playing us all along.
لقد كانوا يلعبون بنا طوال الوقت.
The VP wasn't the target.
نائب الرئيس لم يكن الهدف.
We were.
لقد كنا.
[Sorello sighs]
[تنهد الأخ]
[unsettling music builds up]
[تتصاعد الموسيقى المزعجة]
[Owens] Come on.
[أوينز] تعال.
- No signal? - No, nothing.
- لا يوجد إشارة؟ - لا، لا شيء.
Did you try the door?
هل جربت الباب؟
Yeah, I tried.
نعم لقد حاولت.
Okay. Looks like we're back in business here.
حسنًا. يبدو أننا عدنا إلى العمل هنا.
- See if you can access the footage
- انظر إذا كان بإمكانك الوصول إلى اللقطات
from the security cameras.
من كاميرات المراقبة.
When?
متى؟
- Before we arrived. The last 24 hours.
- قبل وصولنا. آخر ٢٤ ساعة.
I'm on it.
انا على ذلك.
- [Halton] Power's going up in the surveillance room.
- [هالتون] الطاقة ترتفع في غرفة المراقبة.
- Wow. At least one thing's going right.
- واو. على الأقل شيء واحد يسير على ما يرام.
- There's still no internet signal,
- لا يزال لا يوجد إشارة الإنترنت،
but we got a monitor.
ولكن لدينا شاشة.
[door pings]
[رنين الباب]
[Choi] Ssssh.
[تشوي] شششش.
- [device beeping] - [Choi] What's that beeping?
- [صوت تنبيه الجهاز] - [تشوي] ما هذا الصوت؟
Is that coming from the door?
هل هذا قادم من الباب؟
Huh?
هاه؟
No.
لا.
- They're outside! - [explosion]
- إنهم بالخارج! - [انفجار]
[Choi grunts]
[تشوي يتذمر]
- Keep searching, no matter what.
- استمر في البحث مهما كان الأمر.
Just make sure that decoder doesn't fall into their hands.
فقط تأكد من أن جهاز فك التشفير لا يقع في أيديهم.
[Owens] I'm on it.
[أوينز] أنا على هذا الأمر.
[gunshots]
[طلقات نارية]
[Sorello grunts]
[سوريلو يتذمر]
[Sorello] Ah, fuck!
[سوريلو] آه، اللعنة!
Go, go!
إذهب، إذهب!
[Halton] Move it.
[هالتون] حركه.
Clear.
واضح.
Come on, come on, come on.
تعال، تعال، تعال.
Sorello.
أخ.
[Sorello grunting]
[الأخ المتذمر]
- I can help you. Go get the keys.
- يمكنني مساعدتك. اذهب واحضر المفاتيح.
Where were the keys?
أين كانت المفاتيح؟
Keys on the shelf right there.
المفاتيح على الرف هناك.
Get these cuffs off me, man.
أزل هذه الأصفاد عني، يا رجل.
Get up. Come on.
انهض. هيا.
[overlapping grunting]
[تذمر متداخل]
- [Owens] Who the hell are you?
- [أوينز] من أنت بحق الجحيم؟
Come on. Hurry up!
هيا، أسرع!
I could help you, Sorello.
أستطيع مساعدتك، سوريلو.
Pass me the key.
أعطني المفتاح.
Hurry up. Be quick!
أسرع. كن سريعًا!
Throw me the key.
أرميني بالمفتاح.
Trust me.
ثق بي.
[overlapping grunting]
[تذمر متداخل]
[Choi grunts]
[تشوي يتذمر]
Come on, come on, come on!
هيا، هيا، هيا!
Help me. Ow, ow!
ساعدني. أوه، أوه!
Please. Help me.
من فضلك ساعدني.
- Gonna make a tourniquet, all right?
- سأصنع عاصبة، حسنًا؟
It's gonna hurt.
إنه سوف يؤلم.
- Okay, okay. - You ready?
- حسنًا، حسنًا. - هل أنت مستعد؟
One, two...
واحد، اثنان...
[Sorello screaming]
[الأخ الصارخ]
[bomb beeping]
[صوت قنبلة]
Put pressure on it.
ضع ضغطا عليه.
Put the gun down.
ضع البندقية جانبا.
Trust me.
ثق بي.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
- [Anderson] I told you to shoot me.
- [أندرسون] لقد طلبت منك أن تطلق النار علي.
Oh, my god.
يا إلهي.
That's not Anderson!
هذا ليس أندرسون!
[Halton] Fuck you.
[هالتون] اذهب إلى الجحيم.
[Owens gasping]
[أوينز يلهث]
It's about time, brother.
لقد حان الوقت يا أخي.
[Choi groaning]
[تشوي يتأوه]
[Owens gasping]
[أوينز يلهث]
- You would have made life a hell of a lot easier
- لقد جعلت الحياة أسهل كثيرًا
if you just went ahead and died in the street today.
إذا ذهبت للتو ومت في الشارع اليوم.
Sorry to disappoint.
آسف لتخيب الآمال.
[metal scraping] [grunt]
[كشط المعدن] [خرخرة]
[chuckles]
[يضحك]
Attaboy. That's it.
حسنًا. هذا كل شيء.
Breathe.
يتنفس.
Oops.
أُووبس.
Get the decoder.
احصل على فك التشفير.
- You look like a man who just watched a friend die.
- تبدو كرجل شاهد للتو صديقه يموت.
Trust me, I know the feeling.
صدقني، أنا أعرف هذا الشعور.
Anderson. Why?
أندرسون. لماذا؟
His name isn't Anderson.
اسمه ليس أندرسون.
Now, that is true.
الآن، هذا صحيح.
'Cause I killed Anderson this morning.
لأنني قتلت أندرسون هذا الصباح.
Took his badge, all that.
أخذ شارته، كل ذلك.
- Do you know how many people you killed today?
- هل تعلم كم عدد الأشخاص الذين قتلتهم اليوم؟
- You think this country gives a damn?
- هل تعتقد أن هذا البلد يهتم؟
How many kids died fighting in Afghanistan, in Iraq,
كم عدد الأطفال الذين ماتوا وهم يقاتلون في أفغانستان والعراق
on drugs owned by immigrants?
بشأن المخدرات التي يملكها المهاجرون؟
This country is falling apart at the seams,
هذا البلد ينهار في اللحامات،
and only those who truly care about America can save America.
ولا يمكن إلا لأولئك الذين يهتمون حقا بأميركا أن ينقذوها.
What the hell is this?
ما هذا بحق الجحيم؟
It's a crusade, Owens.
إنها حملة صليبية، أوينز.
It's a mother-fucking crusade.
إنها حملة صليبية لعنة الله عليك.
Now for too long, real Americans have been pushed to the side
الآن، ولفترة طويلة جدًا، تم دفع الأمريكيين الحقيقيين إلى الجانب
and made to suffer while others prospered.
وجعلوا الناس يعانون بينما ازدهر آخرون.
You know, 27 veterans commit suicide each day.
هل تعلم أن 27 من المحاربين القدامى ينتحرون كل يوم.
That's nearly 10,000 a year.
وهذا ما يقرب من 10000 في السنة.
This isn't a crusade.
هذه ليست حملة صليبية.
This is fucking nationalist bullshit.
هذا هراء وطني سخيف.
[Owens grunting]
[أوينز يئن]
But the Russians?
ولكن الروس؟
- No. The Russian accent my brother pulled off...
- لا، اللهجة الروسية التي أتقنها أخي...
now, that was child's play.
الآن، كان ذلك مجرد لعبة أطفال.
Diversion.
تحويل.
And while you and your Pentagon are so worried
وبينما أنت وبنتاغونك قلقون للغاية
about the Muhammads and the Karlsruhe,
عن المحمدين وكارلسروه،
y'all forget to worry about the Smiths and the Johnsons.
لقد نسيتم القلق بشأن عائلة سميث وعائلة جونسون.
You got it wrong, son.
لقد أخطأت يا ابني.
We both fought for the same country.
لقد قاتلنا كلينا من أجل نفس البلد.
I know it wasn't perfect when you came home,
أعلم أنه لم يكن مثاليًا عندما عدت إلى المنزل،
but this isn't the way to deal with it.
ولكن هذه ليست الطريقة للتعامل مع الأمر.
- You know, the hardest part of all this
- كما تعلمون، الجزء الأصعب من كل هذا
was keeping a smile off my face when Owens and Choi
كنت أحافظ على الابتسامة بعيدًا عن وجهي عندما كان أوينز وتشوي
brought both devices right here.
لقد جلبت كلا الجهازين إلى هنا.
Now, we may have failed this morning,
الآن، ربما فشلنا هذا الصباح،
but by using the agency's threat notification against you?
ولكن باستخدام إخطار التهديد الصادر من الوكالة ضدك؟
[chuckles] Now, that worked like a charm.
[يضحك] حسنًا، لقد نجح الأمر كالسحر.
Hm?
هممم؟
I'm sorry, Owens.
أنا آسف، أوينز.
Truly am.
انا حقا كذلك.
What it's worth, you died sparking a revolution.
مهما كان الأمر، لقد مت وأنت تشعل الثورة.
I'll carry both your names with me.
سأحمل اسميكما معي.
- [gunshot] - [Halton grunts]
- [طلقة نارية] - [هالتون يئن]
[Owens shudders]
[أوينز يرتجف]
- [Owens] No! - Come here.
- [أوينز] لا! - تعال هنا.
Don't fucking touch me!
لا تلمسني أيها اللعين!
[Owens grunting] [indistinct]
[أوينز يئن] [غير واضح]
[device beeps]
[صوت تنبيه الجهاز]
Get your ass up.
ارفع مؤخرتك.
- Open your fucking eyes. - Fuck you.
- افتح عينيك اللعينة. - اذهب إلى الجحيم.
- Open your eyes. - No, fuck you!
- افتح عينيك. - لا، اذهب إلى الجحيم!
Open your goddamn eyes!
افتح عينيك اللعينة!
You're gonna have to kill me.
سوف يتوجب عليك قتلي.
[Owens screams]
[يصرخ أوينز]
- [Anderson] Come on. -  No!
- [أندرسون] تعال. -  لا!
-  [Anderson] Show me that eye. - [Owens] No.
-  [أندرسون] أرني تلك العين. - [أوينز] لا.
010110.
010110.
- [Computer] Voice activation initiated.
- [الكمبيوتر] بدأ التنشيط الصوتي.
Access granted.
تم منح الوصول
[intense music]
[موسيقى مكثفة]
[alarm blaring]
[صوت الإنذار]
- [Anderson] Destination--mark 38 degrees north,
- [أندرسون] الوجهة--العلامة 38 درجة شمالًا
77 degrees west.
77 درجة غربًا
- All we need is one missile to take out DC.
- كل ما نحتاجه هو صاروخ واحد للقضاء على العاصمة.
You're gonna kill thousands.
سوف تقتل الآلاف.
No, save millions.
لا، احفظ الملايين.
We gotta operate a station in every state.
يتعين علينا تشغيل محطة في كل ولاية.
Once we take back America, we'll make it stronger,
بمجرد أن نستعيد أمريكا، سنجعلها أقوى،
better than ever before.
أفضل من أي وقت مضى.
Who got into your head?
من دخل في رأسك؟
I know you're all twisted up.
أنا أعلم أنكم جميعا ملتوون.
I can--I can help you get out of all this.
أنا أستطيع مساعدتك في الخروج من كل هذا.
We can--we can fix this.
نحن نستطيع-نحن نستطيع إصلاح هذا.
You don't get it!
أنت لا تفهم ذلك!
I don't want to get out of this. For the people I lost.
لا أريد الخروج من هذا، من أجل الأشخاص الذين فقدتهم.
I'm doing this... I'm doing this for my sister.
أنا أفعل هذا... أنا أفعل هذا من أجل أختي.
You remind me of her.
أنت تذكرني بها.
And my real name's Elijah King.
واسمي الحقيقي هو إيليجاه كينج.
You know, I-- I couldn't save her,
كما تعلم، لم أستطع إنقاذها،
but I could save them.
ولكنني أستطيع انقاذهم.
So the next kid that signs up has it better than I did.
لذا فإن الطفل التالي الذي سيسجل لديه وضع أفضل مني.
- You think your sister is proud of you?
- هل تعتقد أن أختك فخورة بك؟
You're not a hero.
أنت لست بطلا.
You're a fucking maniac.
أنت مجنون لعين.
She's all yours.
إنها كلها لك.
Commence launch.
بدء الإطلاق.
- [Computer] Confirmed. 60 seconds.
- [الكمبيوتر] تم التأكيد. 60 ثانية.
[Owens screaming]
[أوينز يصرخ]
Let's go, sweetheart.
دعنا نذهب يا عزيزتي.
[Owens] No.
[أوينز] لا.
[Owens groaning]
[أوينز يتأوه]
Be grateful.
كن شاكرا.
At least you get to die next to your little boyfriend.
على الأقل يمكنك أن تموت بجانب صديقك الصغير.
Go to hell!
اذهب إلى الجحيم!
[bomb beeping]
[صوت قنبلة]
[explosion]
[انفجار]
[gun fired]
[أطلق النار من بندقية]
[Elijah grunting]
[إيليا يتذمر]
Elijah, turn it off.
إيليا، أطفئه.
Do you wanna save lives?
هل تريد انقاذ الارواح؟
Just like me?
مثلي تماما؟
[gunshot]
[طلقة نارية]
[Owens panting]
[أوينز يلهث]
[Elijah groans, thuds]
[إيليا يتأوه، ويصدر صوتًا قويًا]
[soft, dramatic music]
[موسيقى هادئة ودرامية]
[somber music]
[موسيقى حزينة]
- [Marshall] Safe House 5102, do you read?
- [مارشال] البيت الآمن 5102، هل تقرأ؟
Copperhead, do you read?
كوبرهيد، هل تقرأ؟
[tense music]
[موسيقى متوترة]
Safe House 5102, do you read?
البيت الآمن 5102، هل تقرأ؟
Copperhead, do you read?
كوبرهيد، هل تقرأ؟
Elijah, do you read?
إيليا هل تقرأ؟
Damn it, Elijah, pick up the phone.
لعنة عليك يا إيليا، التقط الهاتف.
Elijah, pick up the goddamn phone!
إيليا، التقط الهاتف اللعين!
He's gone.
لقد رحل.
- [Staff] Secure sensitive material.
- [الموظفون] تأمين المواد الحساسة.
Power down.
إيقاف التشغيل
[devices shutting down]
[إغلاق الأجهزة]
- [Female Staff] Wiping all hard drives.
- [الموظفة] مسح جميع محركات الأقراص الصلبة.
He died how he lived, fighting.
لقد مات كما عاش، يقاتل.
And that's how we will remember him.
وهكذا سنتذكره
We will regroup at base at 08:00, Sunday.
سوف نتجمع مرة أخرى في القاعدة في الساعة 08:00، الأحد.
We're just getting started.
لقد بدأنا للتو.
Now let's move to Plan B.
الآن دعونا ننتقل إلى الخطة ب.
You all take the back stairs.
أنتم جميعا تأخذون الدرج الخلفي.
- [Staff] Plan B operation.
- [الموظفون] خطة ب
Move, now!
تحرك الآن!
[Caller] General.
[المتصل] عام
I'm ready for extract.
أنا جاهز للاستخراج.
- [Caller] Copy. ETA, five minutes.
- [المتصل] نسخة. الوقت المتوقع للوصول، خمس دقائق.
See you there.
أراك هناك.
[foreboding music]
[موسيقى تنذر بالسوء]
["I'm on Fire" performed by Wallette] * Been playing a losing game *
[أغنية "أنا مشتعلة" التي يؤديها واليت] * كنت ألعب لعبة خاسرة *
* No way out *
* لا يوجد مخرج *
* Look the devil in the eye *
* انظر إلى الشيطان في عينه *
* He only proved my veins *
*لقد أثبت عروقي فقط*
* Now me and the devil are one and the same *
* الآن أنا والشيطان واحد ونفس الشيء *
* I'm on fire *
*أنا مشتعل*
* Lord, you can't take me *
* يا رب لا يمكنك أن تأخذني *
* It's no matter *
* لا يهم *
* I'm on fire *
*أنا مشتعل*
* But you're the one that's gonna burn *
* لكنك أنت من سيحترق *
* I'm on fire *
*أنا مشتعل*
* Lord, you can't take me. *
* يا رب، لا يمكنك أن تأخذني. *
* It's no matter *
* لا يهم *
* I'm on fire *
*أنا مشتعل*
* But you're the one that's gonna burn *
* لكنك أنت من سيحترق *
* I'm on fire *
*أنا مشتعل*
* Lord, you can't take me. *
* يا رب، لا يمكنك أن تأخذني. *
* It's no matter *
* لا يهم *
* Lord, it's not my turn *
* يا رب ليس دوري *
* Oh, it's not my turn *
* أوه، ليس دوري *
* Yeah *
* نعم *
[ending music theme]
[نهاية الموسيقى الموضوع]